Subaru?
What's wrong?
Just a little nervous.
I mean, considering where
we're headed, y'know?
Yes, you're right.
Ram and Rem are with us this time,
not to mention Meili and
our guide, Lady Anastasia.
And I need to keep you safe, too.
Wait, what?! You're counting me
with the ones who need protecting?!
Oh, dear.
I don't think they like the
mabeast smell I have on me.
Hey, come on, Joseph!
Let her go!
Good boy.
Stroking the neck like this
calms most land dragons.
Huh...
Is that true, Patrasche?
Not for that one, I guess.
Big Brother, don't leave me
alone with that one, all right?
I might just get gobbled up.
Nothing that scary is gonna happen!
Patrasche is a vegetarian!
Subaru. Lady Emilia.
There's something you need
to know about Ram's body.
Got it.
You can ask Ram herself or Beatrice
for more details about the regulation.
Don't worry.
We'll do everything we can for Ram.
Master.
Both ladies are ready to go now.
Good work.
Ram, do take care during your travels.
Thank you for granting my selfish request.
I will not fail to return with
results that meet your expectations.
Subaru... sir...
Be careful.
I will.
Petra and Frederica, hold down
the fort while we're gone.
We will!
Of course.
Right!
We're off to the Auguria Dunes!
What'll it be?
Milk.
And make it cold.
Make mine hot.
Doesn't look like business
is exactly booming here.
Not a lot of customers
during the sand time?
Yeah. And this town doesn't see
a lot of outsiders as it is.
So what are you two doing in
Mirula during the sand time?
I'll tell you. We're going
to conquer the Auguria Dunes!
Let me give you some advice.
Go home before you die.
I can't do that.
There are times when you just
can't back down, you know?
In 400 years,
no one has managed to reach that tower.
The dunes are full of mabeasts
and the witch's miasma.
You can walk forever and never get any
closer to that tower in the distance.
You'll be lucky if you make it back alive.
Most who've tried are still out
there in the sand, asleep forever.
Take my advice and don't do anything dumb—
I'm sorry.
I can tell you're deeply concerned for us.
No. I'm just sick of seeing
young, careless folks like you
end up the same way every time.
Thank you for the drinks.
And thank you for telling
us all that, too.
You've been a big help. Later.
For the past year or so...
folks have been seeing birds
flying over the dunes.
People who've seen 'em say they're
always heading toward that tower.
So if you do get lost, look for a bird.
If you're lucky, it might
show you the way.
Mister...
Then again, if you're already lost
out there with nowhere to turn,
you've clearly got the
worst luck imaginable.
The Pleiades Watchtower.
The tower of the sage with a history, huh?
How have your spirits
been since that happened?
Nothing has changed.
They stay by my side,
but they seem perplexed.
My Divine Protection of Guiding
Spirits seems to be intact.
They seem unsure why they find
it difficult to leave my side.
So I guess even though they forgot
you, the contract isn't broken.
Which means, right now,
I can only fulfill my duty as
a knight with my swordsmanship.
It's a fact that without my spirit arts,
my capacity has dropped significantly.
Why do you appear even
more vexed than I am?
Who said I was?! Don't go
saying whatever you want!
Why would I be
vexed because you're weaker?!
Who told you that?!
You are less suited to keeping
secrets than I realized.
Perhaps it's because I've been
traveling with you for a while,
but I feel as though I've
come to understand you.
Well, same here!
If this keeps up and nothing else happens,
I'm gonna be an authority on you
by the time we reach the tower.
Not to worry.
Excluding myself, you are
already undeniably the one
who knows me better than
anyone in the world.
Damn it, I got myself stuck
with a title I never wanted!
Subaru!
You can't keep playing
around forever, I suppose.
The sand time is about to start.
Hang in there, Patrasche!
You, too, Joseph!
We've got wind and miasma,
and we need to watch out for mabeasts, too!
And to make sure we don't lose sight
of the tower and get lost, I suppose.
I dunno, I feel like it'd be harder
to lose sight of that thing.
Betty agrees with you,
but anything can happen here, I suppose.
The fact that no one has ever
made it there proves it.
True.
Lady Anastasia?
What's goin' on?
You're sure we just need
to keep going straight?
Aw, Natsuki, why're ya
so suspicious of me?
We're in the same boat here.
You can trust me.
Trusting a fox is easier
said than done, I suppose.
Oh? You told her, Natsuki?
Well, Lady Anastasia wouldn't
particularly care, right?
Ya got that right, Natsuki!
You needn't worry.
I will keep my promise.
And what about you, Meili?
You doing your job?
We haven't run into a single mabeast
since we entered the dunes, have we?
What? That's because of you?
Oh, you have to ask?
Then I'll show you just how
much you should appreciate me.
There! All done!
What was...
It was a sandworm.
I don't recall any records
of one that large, though.
Well? Starting to see me
in a different light now?
Man, I'm dying to get out of
these dunes and into a bathtub!
I'm with ya there.
But you two must have
realized it by now, right?
Yeah, I get it.
We've been heading straight
for it all this time...
But we aren't getting
any closer to the tower.
This must be why Reinhard
never made it there.
The space around here is warped.
The space is warped?
Basically, it seems like the dunes
and the tower are connected,
but they're not.
We might actually just be
runnin' around in circles.
And that's why the Auguria
Dunes are so dangerous?
It makes sense.
So are we also gonna be overpowered
by the distortion in space
that's sunk so many adventurers?
That's why I volunteered to guide
y'all to the Pleiades Watchtower.
When a merchant heads out
to make a purchase,
they're headin' out to win.
Are you saying you can
see a path to the tower?
The sand time, when the wind picks up,
is the recoil from space twistin'
and returnin' to normal.
In other words, the periods
between the sand times
are when the distortion's lettin' up.
And through those cracks
is the real sea of sand that's
connected to the tower.
The real sea of sand...
And the one who's gonna play the vital
role of findin' those cracks is...
We need your clairvoyance to see
through the eyes of mabeasts.
If there are mabeasts that stay
active during the sand time,
there must be some that come across
the cracks in space somewhere.
A bit more to the north.
Is it a sandworm?
And to find them, we have
Meili locate the mabeasts
and tell Miss Ram where they are.
It's no use.
I've lost the connection.
Subaru, we can't put Ram through any more.
Lady Emilia.
There is no one else suited to this.
This is a job only I can do.
Meili, you can leave out the
mabeasts that are underground.
There's no point when all I can see is sand.
I can't tell them apart that well.
Maybe you should stop giving
up on them right away?
I don't think the idea in itself is wrong.
It's just a matter of meetin'
the right mabeast, I guess.
If we're calling this a contest of luck,
we're at a huge disadvantage.
A bird?
Can't believe a bird would
wanna fly through this sky.
A bird?
Natsuki?
Subaru! Is there a bird?
Yeah!
Ram, can you see through a bird's eyes?
What do you mean?
Those birds are the key!
I've got it!
Yes!
This time, we're gonna make
it through the sand time!
Let's go!
Straight. Keep going straight.
Please get us out!
I don't want to put them through any more!
Please!
We did it! We're out!
We did it! We did it!
Hey! Quit screaming in my ears, I suppose!
Aw, no need to put on airs!
Show some joy!
Come on! Banzai!
Grr, I say.
Banzai... I suppose.
Look at that! It's proof
we've made it to a new stage!
The dunes turned into an
endless field of flowers...
An endless field of... flowers?
They're oiran bears.
Subaru, what happened?
Ram's clairvoyance suddenly—
Stop.
Emilia-tan, stay calm.
Keep quiet.
Shh. Don't move.
No!
Run!
They're coming! They're coming!
Hah! Yah! There! Take that!
Take a whole bunch of them!
Yeah! That's my Emilia-tan!
Barusu, if you don't want to die,
make that thing run for all it's worth!
Of course I—wait, Ram?!
I cannot allow Lady Emilia
to shoulder all the work.
Damn! I can't let him beat me!
Beako, you ready?!
Of course I am!
It's you who'd better not
run out of gas, I suppose!
Minya!
Go, sandworm!
Crush 'em all!
We're almost there!
We just gotta charge straight
for the watchtower!
What—
Huh?
I died? And went back?
Why? When?!
What happened?!
How did I die?!
Shit, shit, shit, shi—
No! Juli—
Damn it! Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
Hah! Yah! There! Take that!
Subaru!
Beatrice...
Minya!
I've got something for you!
Sandworm!
Go!
Crap! This is going exactly
the same way as before!
Barusu, if you don't want to die,
make that thing run for all it's worth!
Ram! Don't head for the tower!
We gotta find another route!
What are you saying?!
It's a straight line, and every
other path is full of mabeasts!
We can't go straight to it!
We have to change directions!
Ram!
Do as Subaru says!
He would never just blurt out
something silly without a reason!
Barusu speaks nonsense and
falsehoods on a daily basis!
He would never just blurt out something
silly for no reason when we're in danger!
Thanks for the rephrase!
You two up top, don't get shaken off!
Dodge!
That was close.
Subaru, we messed up!
Huh?
We got separated from Emilia's
carriage, I suppose!
It's just you and Betty!
What?!
Damn it, beating that bastard
Regulus was easier than this!
No time for complaining, I suppose!
We have to find—
I know!
I'm thinking!
What... just...
Subaru!
Subaru! Subaru!
No! You can't die!
Don't die!
Don't leave me alone...
Don't!
Don't leave Betty behind...
Suba—
The first and second death were both...
Beako, I love you.
Huh?
Invisible Providence!
Good boy.
There's something I want to ask you guys.
Did anyone else see a flash of
light coming from the tower?
A light from the tower?
Yeah.
What do you think this light was?
I... think it's something dangerous.
Definitely not friendly, at least.
Based only on a hunch?
Well... yeah.
I see. That's troubling.
It's just a hunch! You believe me?
It's your hunch.
So I think it's worth worrying about.
Oh...
Ram?
It's looking...
at Barusu?
I won't let you!
A needle?
Barusu! Another one's coming!
Beako, you ready?!
Obviously!
E-M-T!
I suppose!
This is...
Absolute nullification magic, E-M-T.
All magic loses its effect
within this field.
The catch is... it doesn't last long.
What?!
We messed up!
E-M-T is making the distortion
in space come undone!
I get it! The sand time works the
same way as Beako's Door Crossing!
I found you.
Overcome Sand Time